# Bogdan Gorelkin

Book the meeting instantly: <a href="https://calendly.com/b-gorelkin">https://calendly.com/b-gorelkin</a>

b.k.gorelkin@gmail.com +33768919872 in in/bogdan-gorelkin/

bogdangorelkin.github.io b.gorelkin BogdanGorelkin Paris, France

## **SUMMARY**

Full-stack software developer with over 3 years of experience in building scalable, cross-platform applications with solid architecture. My skills allow me to mentor and manage junior developers, ensuring the quality of the application being developed.

I am capable of independently deploying applications from scratch, choosing the appropriate technology stack. In addition, start-ups come to me for independent development advice.

Driven by ambition, hard work, and versatility, I bring a strong work ethic to find elegant solutions to your challenging projects.

## **SKILLS**

Programming languages: JavaScript (TypeScript), Java, Python

FrontEnd: HTML, SASS, SCSS, CSS

Frameworks: React, React-Native, Svelte

BackEnd: NodeJS, ExpressJS, NestJS, Java Spring, Flask

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Software Application Developer, AuxaSphere

Jun 2023 - Now | FR, Paris (La Défense)

Development and support a suite of applications for secure and reliable digital data exchange

- Independent development of cross-platform applications with selection of technologies from PoC to MVP
- Design and implementation of new features and microservices
- · Mentoring, refactoring, optimization and code review

Software Application Developer, AuxaSphere (TemmaCare) Jan 2022 - Jun 2023 | FR, Paris (La Défense)

Development of hardware/software system for remote medical diagnostics

- · Medical devices data visualization, its encryption, storage and delivery
- Designing and implementing the UX & UI for a multi-role system
- Building reusable packages with strict typing

#### Research Engineer, Inria & Femto-ST

Oct 2020 - Sep 2021 | FR, Lille

Development and design of modular robots with dynamic configurations

- Writing instructions and documentation for the new BIP programming paradigm
- Creation of rules for the behavior of modules and their interaction with each other in composite systems
- System description using deterministic finite state machines
- Strengthening the time synchronization protocol for modular robots
- Implementation of synchronization algorithms for modular robots

## Research Engineer, Polytech Nantes

Jan 2020 - Jul 2020 | FR, Nantes

Embedded device security research system development

- Implementation of the RSA crypto algorithm on the STM32 microcontroller
- Investigation of vulnerabilities via third-party side channels using DMA.

## **EDUCATION**

**Master of Internet of Things,** Université Bourgogne Franche-Comté, Montbéliard, 2020 - 2021 The 7th engineering school in France

**Master of Wireless Embedded Technologies (double diploma),** Polytech de Nantes, 2019 - 2020 First student in exchange partnership with TUSUR.

Master of Communication Systems and the Internet of Things, TUSUR Tomsk 2018-2020 The leading Russian university in the fields of control systems, radioelectronics, and biomedical technologies.

Bachelor of Audio Visual Technologies, TUSUR, Tomsk 2014-2018

## Other

Languages: French (B2), English (B2), German (A1), Russian (native) Skills: MongoDB, Docker, RabbitMQ, Redis, Git, CI/CD, Linux, SSH, Shell, C, C++, Arduino, MicroPython, ROS, RTOS, PCB, CubeMX, LaTeX, Soldering

#### SIDE PROJECTS

- Cross-platform music app for distributing tracks with limited listening rights
- Social network, designed to encourage users to engage in various outdoor activities

#### **INTERESTS**

My hobbies are automation and smart device development (IoT). In my free time, I create controller-based devices and run my own home server with a Raspberry Pi.

I express myself artistically through music, playing multiple instruments. Passionate about various sports such as cycling, bouldering, rollerblading, and table tennis. I also cultivate my interest in mechanics by repairing vehicles, from cars to scooters.

My multifaceted interests reflect my relentless curiosity and commitment to continuous learning.